And at the end I click on create and I wait a little bit. It is again going to remove another credit of mine
But it doesn't matter. So I'll wait
So I tried three times and as you see it's removing my credits, but it says something went wrong on our end, right?
So what I do is that I reload the page, I copy my command and I reload the page and
Wait and yes, I again come and add my command over here. I come to images. I add a click on add image and
Wait
Until I can see my
Own logo
Uploaded to designer. This is probably the folder that I need to be looking for
Oh, we have nothing uploaded to designer. Wow. What about pictures?
So yeah, it's now available. So I click on the logo and I click select the size yep, and I click on create again
Yeah, so as you see it says something's wrong on our end, please try again later
Whatever. Again, it's removed another credit of mine as you see.